[See Your Love]
[انظر حبك]
[Episode 5]
[الحلقة 5]
Jiang Shaopeng.
جيانغ شاوبنغ.
About yesterday...
عن الأمس...
[Resignation]
[استقالة]
Jiang Shaopeng.
جيانغ شاوبنغ.
Jiang Shaopeng, are you serious?
جيانغ شاوبنغ، هل أنت جاد؟
You don't want to join Xin'an Long-term Care Center?
ألا تريد الانضمام إلى مركز شينآن للرعاية طويلة الأمد؟
Don't be like this! I'm sorry!
لا تكن هكذا! أنا آسف!
I worked very hard
لقد عملت بجد
and took good care of you.
واهتم بك جيدا.
Wait. Wait.
انتظر انتظر.
I don't know what your gestures mean!
لا أعرف ماذا تعني تصرفاتك!
I don't allow you to resign!
لا أسمح لك بالاستقالة!
You're like a couple quarreling.
أنتم مثل زوجين يتشاجران.
What did you do to make him so angry that he wants to resign?
ماذا فعلت حتى أغضبه هذا الأمر حتى أراد الاستقالة؟
I...
أنا...
He...
هو...
Did you take advantage of him?
هل استفدت منه؟
Jiang Shaopeng!
جيانغ شاوبنغ!
If so, don't you feel guilty towards your...
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، ألا تشعر بالذنب تجاه...؟
Shut up!
اسكت!
Jiang Shaopeng!
جيانغ شاوبنغ!
He can't hear you.
لا يستطيع سماعك.
I'm just telling the truth.
انا فقط أقول الحقيقة.
Why are you looking at me like that?
لماذا تنظر إلي هكذا؟
It'll be your responsibility
ستكون مسؤوليتك
to take care of me.
للاعتناء بي.
From today...
من اليوم...
From now on.
من الآن فصاعدا.
I'm very busy.
أنا مشغول جداً.
Seriously?
بجد؟
[He hates vegetables, especially green peppers and carrots] [He likes beef, shrimps, and cheese]
[يكره الخضروات، وخاصة الفلفل الأخضر والجزر] [يحب لحم البقر والروبيان والجبن]
[He favors sweet flavors]
[إنه يفضل النكهات الحلوة]
[He has stomach problems]
[لديه مشاكل في المعدة]
[Avoid pungent food]
[تجنب الأطعمة ذات النكهة اللاذعة]
[He's a picky eater]
[إنه من الصعب إرضاؤه في الطعام]
[He likes beef, shrimps, and cheese]
[يحب لحم البقر والروبيان والجبن]
[He hates vegetables]
[يكره الخضروات]
[Especially green peppers and carrots]
[وخاصة الفلفل الأخضر والجزر]
[He's like a child]
[إنه مثل الطفل]
[He hates vegetables, especially green peppers and carrots] [He likes beef, shrimps, and cheese]
[يكره الخضروات، وخاصة الفلفل الأخضر والجزر] [يحب لحم البقر والروبيان والجبن]
I didn't expect him to be so thoughtful.
لم أتوقع أن يكون عميق التفكير إلى هذا الحد.
He's a great carer.
إنه مقدم رعاية عظيم.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
When eating alone, I never know what to buy.
عندما أتناول الطعام بمفردي، لا أعرف أبدًا ماذا أشتري.
Son!
ابن!
Your boss is finally willing to let you have a day off and go home.
أخيرًا أصبح رئيسك في العمل على استعداد للسماح لك بأخذ يوم إجازة والعودة إلى المنزل.
I've finished my job.
لقد انتهيت من عملي.
It must be because you took good care of him.
لا بد أن يكون ذلك بسبب اهتمامك الجيد به.
Awesome!
مذهل!
What are you going to cook today?
ماذا ستطبخ اليوم؟
If I'm alone,
إذا كنت وحدي،
a simple meal is enough.
وجبة بسيطة تكفي.
But now that you're back,
ولكن الآن بعد أن عدت،
of course I should cook what you like.
بالطبع يجب أن أطبخ ما تحبينه.
You've lost weight.
لقد فقدت وزنك.
It's just
إنه فقط
what you think.
ما هو رأيك.
Where did you learn that?
أين تعلمت ذلك؟
Good for you.
جيدة بالنسبة لك.
Auntie, what are we having for dinner tonight?
عمة، ماذا سنأكل على العشاء الليلة؟
Shaopeng?
شاوبنج؟
Why are you home?
لماذا انت في المنزل؟
Are you having a day off?
هل لديك يوم عطلة؟
I've finished my job.
لقد انتهيت من عملي.
I see.
أرى.
Then today,
ثم اليوم،
let's drink wine.
دعونا نشرب النبيذ.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
Auntie!
عمة!
Where is the plum wine I brought back from Japan last time?
أين نبيذ البرقوق الذي أحضرته من اليابان في المرة الأخيرة؟
I think it's over there.
أعتقد أنه هناك.
Let's drink it later
دعونا نشربه لاحقا
to celebrate since Shaopeng has finished his first job.
للاحتفال بأن شاوبنج أنهى وظيفته الأولى.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Do you need help?
هل تحتاج الى مساعدة؟
Okay, come in first.
حسنًا، تعال أولاً.
Okay.
تمام.
[Basic health information]
[معلومات صحية أساسية]
[Self-assessment of health]
[التقييم الذاتي للصحة]
[I want your health report and food preferences]
[أريد تقريرك الصحي وتفضيلاتك الغذائية]
No problem. Take care of me from now on.
لا مشكلة، اعتني بي من الآن فصاعدًا.
Little Boss!
رئيس صغير!
Impressive.
بديع.
You actually have found me.
لقد وجدتني فعلا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I didn't expect him to be so thoughtful.
لم أتوقع أن يكون عميق التفكير إلى هذا الحد.
Jiang Shaopeng!
جيانغ شاوبنغ!
What did you do to make him so angry that he wants to resign?
ماذا فعلت حتى أغضبه هذا الأمر حتى أراد الاستقالة؟
He's a great carer.
إنه مقدم رعاية عظيم.
[He hates vegetables, especially green peppers and carrots] [He likes beef, shrimps, and cheese]
[يكره الخضروات، وخاصة الفلفل الأخضر والجزر] [يحب لحم البقر والروبيان والجبن]
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
[Self-assessment of health]
[التقييم الذاتي للصحة]
Be careful.
احرص.
Okay.
تمام.
He got drunk after just three drinks.
لقد سكر بعد ثلاثة مشروبات فقط.
He has a low alcohol tolerance just like his father.
إن قدرته على تحمل الكحول منخفضة تمامًا مثل والده.
The alcohol content is 15%.
نسبة الكحول 15%.
He's already quite impressive.
إنه مثير للإعجاب بالفعل.
This boy...
هذا الصبي...
Do you think
هل تعتقد
he really has finished his job or he got fired?
هل انتهى فعلا من عمله أم تم طرده؟
Whatever he says.
مهما قال .
If we are too worried and ask too much,
إذا كنا قلقين للغاية وطلبنا الكثير،
we'll only put him under a lot of pressure.
سنضعه فقط تحت قدر كبير من الضغط.
And he'll think it's all his fault.
وسيعتقد أن كل هذا خطؤه.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
He's been trying so hard just to make us rest assured.
لقد كان يحاول جاهدا أن يجعلنا مطمئنين.
If I had noticed something was wrong with him
لو لاحظت أن هناك خطأ ما معه
after the doctor administered the medication
بعد أن أعطى الطبيب الدواء
that year when Shaopeng fell ill,
في ذلك العام عندما مرض شاوبنج،
we wouldn't have missed the chance for emergency treatment.
لم نكن لنفوت فرصة العلاج الطارئ.
It's all in the past.
كل هذا في الماضي .
Auntie.
خالة.
It was not anyone's fault.
لم يكن خطأ أحد.
Didn't we agree
ألم نتفق
to look ahead and never look back?
أن ننظر إلى الأمام ولا ننظر إلى الوراء أبدا؟
Look ahead.
انظر إلى الأمام.
Never look back.
لا تنظر للخلف ابدًا.
I'll let you eat
سأدعك تأكل
after you handle this file.
بعد التعامل مع هذا الملف.
I can order takeout
أستطيع أن أطلب الطعام الجاهز
with my smartphone.
مع هاتفي الذكي.
The file is in your hands.
الملف بين يديك .
You can eat only after you handle it.
لا يمكنك تناول الطعام إلا بعد التعامل معه.
You know I can't understand it.
أنت تعرف أنني لا أستطيع أن أفهم ذلك.
Why are you making things difficult for me?
لماذا تجعل الأمور صعبة بالنسبة لي؟
It's already three minutes.
لقد مرت ثلاث دقائق بالفعل.
My instant noodles…
نودلز سريعة التحضير
Are you really so useless?
هل أنت حقا عديم الفائدة؟
Yes.
نعم.
That's why I advised you to work for another boss as soon as possible.
ولهذا السبب نصحتك بالعمل مع رئيس آخر في أقرب وقت ممكن.
You'll have no future sticking with me.
لن يكون لديك مستقبل في البقاء معي.
President doesn't think so.
الرئيس لا يعتقد ذلك.
He has high expectations of you.
لديه توقعات عالية منك.
Not every expectation can be met.
ليس من الممكن تلبية كل التوقعات.
I'm just not that capable.
أنا لست قادرة على ذلك.
Hengfeng Group will go bankrupt if it's handed over to you.
مجموعة Hengfeng سوف تعلن إفلاسها إذا تم تسليمها إليك.
I think so too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضًا.
Stinky tofu?
التوفو نتن؟
Or oyster omelettes?
أو عجة المحار؟
I'm not hungry.
أنا لست جائعا.
If only Jiang Shaopeng were here.
لو كان جيانج شاو بنج هنا.
Go get him back.
اذهب واحضره مرة أخرى.
We'll leave in 30 minutes.
سنغادر في 30 دقيقة.
I...
أنا...
He really slammed the door in my face again.
لقد أغلق الباب في وجهي مرة أخرى.
Who is it? Why won't you open the door?
من هو؟ لماذا لا تفتح الباب؟
Mr. Yang.
السيد أيّ.
Your former boss?
رئيسك السابق؟
You've finished your job.
لقد انتهيت من مهمتك.
Why did he come to you?
لماذا جاء إليك؟
Something happened?
هل حدث شيء؟
So you haven't finished your job.
إذن لم تنتهي من مهمتك.
Is there...
هل هناك...
some misunderstanding?
بعض سوء الفهم؟
Or...
أو...
did you quarrel?
هل تشاجرتم؟
Go buy salt for me.
اذهب واشتري لي الملح.
Boss, hello.
مرحبا يا رئيس.
Go. Go.
إذهب.إذهب.
Buy salt.
اشتري الملح.
Buy salt for me.
اشتري لي الملح.
You know which brand I like.
أنت تعرف ما هي العلامة التجارية التي أحبها.
Go buy salt!
اذهب لشراء الملح!
I'll go buy salt with him.
سأذهب لشراء الملح معه.
I'll send him back later.
سأرسله مرة أخرى في وقت لاحق.
Okay.
تمام.
Take your time.
خذ وقتك.
I'm not in urgent need of it.
أنا لست في حاجة ماسة إليه.
[I can't hear or speak] [Don't worry. I won't tell Cheng Fengjie]
[لا أستطيع أن أسمع أو أتحدث] [لا تقلق. لن أخبر تشنغ فينججي]
I do want you to keep it a secret,
أريدك أن تبقي الأمر سرا،
but I came here mainly to apologize to you.
ولكنني أتيت إلى هنا في المقام الأول للاعتذار لك.
[I'm sorry that I used you]
[أنا آسف لأنني استخدمتك]
I'm sorry that I used you.
أنا آسف لأنني استغلتك.
No matter what the reason is,
مهما كان السبب،
I can't justify using you.
لا أستطيع تبرير استخدامك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I hope you can accept my apology
أتمنى أن تقبل اعتذاري
and continue to take care of me.
واستمر في الاعتناء بي.
Please.
لو سمحت.
[You drew them?]
[أنت رسمتهم؟]
Yes.
نعم.
My...
لي...
interest.
اهتمام.
[Why did you leave?]
[لماذا رحلت؟]
Now, the whole family pays much attention
الآن أصبحت العائلة بأكملها تولي اهتمامًا كبيرًا
to your performance in Taiwan.
إلى أدائك في تايوان.
You can't handle it.
لا يمكنك التعامل مع هذا.
Do you know what people say about you behind your back?
هل تعلم ماذا يقول الناس عنك خلف ظهرك؟
Useless rich kid.
طفل غني عديم الفائدة.
Um.
واحد.
[Why did you leave?]
[لماذا رحلت؟]
My dad wants me to take over the family business.
يريد والدي أن أتولى إدارة أعمال العائلة.
But I don't want to.
ولكنني لا أريد ذلك.
I want him to hand it over to my cousin.
أريد أن يسلمها إلى ابن عمي.
He's very outstanding and capable.
إنه متميز وقادر للغاية.
But my dad doesn't like him.
لكن والدي لا يحبه.
[Why didn't you tell your dad?]
[لماذا لم تخبر والدك؟]
I dare not.
لا أجرؤ.
And he only wants to hear what he wants to hear.
وهو لا يريد إلا أن يسمع ما يريد سماعه.
I'm useless, right?
أنا عديم الفائدة، أليس كذلك؟
[You just love your dad very much and you don't want to let him down]
[أنت تحب والدك كثيرًا ولا تريد أن تخذليه]
Continue to take care of me.
استمر في الاهتمام بي.
[Your leg has recovered]
[لقد تعافت ساقك]
I'm still injured.
لا أزال مصابًا.
Here.
هنا.
And it hurts a lot here.
ويؤلمني كثيرا هنا.
[I need to go home to get my luggage first]
[أحتاج إلى العودة إلى المنزل للحصول على أمتعتي أولاً]
That's all for today's meeting.
هذا كل شيء بالنسبة لاجتماع اليوم.
Ken, remind the department in charge to keep an eye on the progress.
كين، ذكّر القسم المسؤول بمراقبة التقدم.
Yes.
نعم.
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I hope you like today's tea.
أتمنى أن يعجبك شاي اليوم.
It's great.
إنه لشيء رائع.
I like it very much.
انا احبه كثيرا.
[Meet me at 10:30 in Room 1213 at Ouyou Hotel]
[قابلني في الساعة 10:30 صباحًا في الغرفة 1213 في فندق Ouyou]
Stay away from my subordinate.
ابتعد عن مرؤوسيك.
He took the initiative.
لقد أخذ المبادرة.
That's it?
هذا كل شيء؟
No punishment?
لا عقاب؟
What I value is his competence.
ما أقدّره هو كفاءته.
Then you should change your attitude towards me.
إذن يجب عليك أن تغير موقفك تجاهي.
I'm very competent.
أنا كفء للغاية.
Indeed, you're competent.
في الواقع، أنت كفء.
But my attitude towards you is purely personal.
لكن موقفي تجاهك هو موقف شخصي بحت.
It has nothing to do with your competence.
ليس له علاقة بكفاءتك.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
has your Little Boss recovered?
هل تعافى رئيسك الصغير؟
He really wants you to pretend to be Yang Zixiang
إنه يريدك حقًا أن تتظاهر بأنك يانغ زيكسيانج
and work on behalf of him?
والعمل لصالحه؟
You are doing this intentionally, aren't you?
أنت تفعل هذا عمدا، أليس كذلك؟
You know I hate green peppers.
أنت تعرف أنني أكره الفلفل الأخضر.
[You promised me you'd listen to me]
[لقد وعدتني بأنك ستستمع إلي]
Half, okay?
نصف ، حسنًا؟
Are we brothers?
هل نحن اخوة؟
You love to hold grudges.
أنت تحب أن تحمل الضغائن.
[We'll be if you eat all of them]
[سنكون كذلك إذا أكلتهم جميعًا]
You know what I was saying?
هل تعلم ماذا كنت أقول؟
You can read lips?
هل تستطيع قراءة الشفاه؟
Then why did you use your smartphone?
إذن لماذا استخدمت هاتفك الذكي؟
My dad wants me to take over the family business.
يريد والدي أن أتولى إدارة أعمال العائلة.
[I dare not, and he only wants to hear what he wants to hear]
[لا أجرؤ، وهو يريد فقط أن يسمع ما يريد سماعه]
[Life is a schedule measured in hours] [My mom passed away a long time ago. Since I started to remember things...]
[الحياة عبارة عن جدول زمني يقاس بالساعات] [توفيت والدتي منذ زمن طويل. ومنذ بدأت أتذكر أشياء...]
[It was hard to read your lips. But I'm used to it now. I can understand most of it] [We weren't close back then, so I couldn't understand the way your mouth moves when you speak]
[كان من الصعب قراءة شفتيك. لكنني اعتدت على ذلك الآن. أستطيع فهم معظم ما تقوله] [لم نكن قريبين في ذلك الوقت، لذا لم أستطع فهم الطريقة التي تتحرك بها شفتاك عندما تتحدث]
When I talked about the job with you back then,
عندما تحدثت معك عن الوظيفة في ذلك الوقت،
what I told Jonathan...
ما قلته لجوناثان...
what I told Cheng Fengjie...
ما قلته لتشينغ فنغ جي...
You're worried the person hired would be a leaker.
أنت قلق من أن الشخص الذي تم تعيينه سيكون مسربًا.
It's perfect that he can't hear us.
من المثالي أنه لا يستطيع أن يسمعنا.
We'll be brothers after I eat all of them.
سوف نصبح إخوة بعد أن آكلهم جميعًا.
Can we be friends and brothers now?
هل يمكننا أن نكون أصدقاء وأخوة الآن؟
Do you think I'm a kid?
هل تعتقد أنني طفل؟
Have you found the people who tried to assassinate Yang Zixiang?
هل وجدتم الأشخاص الذين حاولوا اغتيال يانغ زيكسيانغ؟
Keep looking.
استمر بالبحث.
I'll pay attention to it in Taiwan.
سأنتبه لذلك في تايوان.
Give the knife back to me!
أعطني السكين مرة أخرى!
You again.
انت مرة أخرى.
It was your first time killing someone, right?
لقد كانت هذه المرة الأولى التي تقتل فيها شخصًا، أليس كذلك؟
You didn't even know how to choose the right time or place to do it.
ولم تعرف حتى كيفية اختيار الوقت أو المكان المناسب للقيام بذلك.
It's none of your business!
إنه ليس من شأنك!
Remember, don't make a sound when you attack from behind
تذكر، لا تصدر صوتًا عندما تهاجم من الخلف
to avoid being noticed by your target.
لتجنب أن يلاحظك هدفك.
What you are doing now is really stupid.
ما تفعله الآن غبي حقًا.
Shut up!
اسكت!
But it's much better
لكن الأمر أفضل بكثير
than your sex skills.
من مهاراتك الجنسية.
Bastard!
نذل!
I won't let you go.
لن أتركك تذهب.
I'll definitely outshine you!
بالتأكيد سوف أتفوق عليك!
In which aspect?
في أي جانب؟
He's like an idiot.
إنه مثل الأحمق.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Brother Dong.
الأخ دونغ.
I've found Yang Zixiang's special assistant.
لقد وجدت المساعد الخاص لـ يانغ زيكسيانج.
I'll continue to follow him
سأستمر في متابعته
and find Yang Zixiang.
وابحث عن Yang Zixiang.
Who sent you here?
من أرسلك إلى هنا؟
Have you ever complained that you can't hear?
هل سبق لك أن اشتكيت من عدم قدرتك على السمع؟
[Moments of seeing love]
[لحظات رؤية الحب]
[I'm sorry that I used you]
[أنا آسف لأنني استخدمتك]
[No matter what the reason is, I can't justify using you. I'm sorry]
[مهما كان السبب، لا أستطيع تبرير استخدامك. أنا آسف]
[I hope you can accept my apology and continue to take care of me]
[أتمنى أن تقبل اعتذاري وتستمر في رعايتي]
[Please]
[لو سمحت]